<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Marek Petrik</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Marek Petrik</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/cv/</guid>
      <description>CV Please see the PDF version of my CV.
About Marek Marek Petrik is an assistant professor of Computer Science at the University of New Hampshire. Until 2016, he was a research staff member at the Mathematical Sciences Department of IBM&amp;rsquo;s T. J. Watson Research Center. He received his Ph.D. in Computer Science in 2010 from the University of Massachusetts, Amherst. His research focuses on developing better methods for safe, robust, and risk-averse reinforcement learning and their applications to domains that involve high-stakes decisions under uncertainty.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/publications/</guid>
      <description>Publications and Presentations Recent Preprints Soft-Robust Algorithms for Batch Reinforcement Learning, Elita A. Lobo, Mohammad Ghavamzadeh, Marek Petrik, 2021.
Journals and Selective Conferences 2021 Partial Policy Iteration for L1-Robust Markov Decision Processes, Chin Pang Ho, Marek Petrik, Wolfram Wiesemann, Forthcoming in Journal of Machine Learning Research, 2021.
Optimizing Percentile Criterion using Robust MDPs, Bahram Behzadian, Reazul Hasan Russel, Marek Petrik, Chin Pang Ho, Artificial Intelligence and Statistics (AISTATS), 2021.
Robust Behavior Cloning with Adversarial Demonstration Detection, Mostafa Hussein, Brendan Crowe, et al.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/teaching/adv_topics_ml_16/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/teaching/adv_topics_ml_16/</guid>
      <description>CS980: Advanced Machine Learning Where Kingsbury N233
When MW 3:40pm - 5:00pm
What In this seminar, we will cover how to make good decisions using machine learning. Reinforcement learning and multi-armed bandits are just some of the methods that combine decision making with machine learning. These methods play a crucial role in countless real problems such as when personalizing websites, navigating robots, managing supply chains and revenue, and even when playing Go!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/teaching/adv_topics_ml_17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/teaching/adv_topics_ml_17/</guid>
      <description>CS980: Advanced ML: Reinforcement Learning Please see the class homepage for schedule and other up-to-date information.
Where Kingsbury N233
When MW 3:40pm - 5:00pm
What In this seminar, we will cover reinforcement learning, or how to make good decisions driven by data. The goal in reinforcement learning is to learn how to act while interacting with a dynamic and complex environment. Reinforcement learning methods can be applied in various domains, such as when managing ecosystems, optimizing website, to robotics, and healthcare.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/teaching/aml_18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/teaching/aml_18/</guid>
      <description>CS980: Advanced ML: Reinforcement Learning Please see the class homepage for schedule and other up-to-date information.
Where and When  Kingsbury N233 MW 3:40pm - 5:00pm  What This seminar will cover reinforcement learning. The goal in reinforcement learning is to learn how to act while interacting with a dynamic and complex environment. Instead of trying to cover all reinforcement learning topics, we will focus on the foundations needed to understand other concepts.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/teaching/aml_19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/teaching/aml_19/</guid>
      <description>CS980: Advanced ML: Reinforcement Learning Please see the class homepage for more information.
Where and When  Kingsbury N233 TR 3:40pm - 5:00pm  What This seminar will cover reinforcement learning. The goal in reinforcement learning is to learn how to act while interacting with a dynamic and complex environment. Instead of trying to cover all reinforcement learning topics, we will focus on the foundations needed to understand other concepts. Below are some examples of relevant topics:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/teaching/intro_ml_17/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/teaching/intro_ml_17/</guid>
      <description>CS780 / CS880: Introduction to Machine Learning When and Where Tue &amp;amp; Thu, 12:40 pm - 2:00 pm Kingsbury N133
See class overview for more information on textbooks, syllabus, assignments, office hours, and grading.
Assignments Please use Piazza for questions about assignments.
   Assignment Due Date     Assignment 1 2/14/17 at 12:40PM   Assignment 2 2/21/17 at 12:40PM   Assignment 3 3/09/17 at 12:40PM   Assignment 4 4/06/17 at 12:40PM   Assignment 5 4/20/17 at 12:40PM    Syllabus    Date Slides Reading Notebooks     1/26 Statistical learning ISL 1,2 (html) (RMD)   1/31 Linear regression I ISL 3.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/teaching/ml_18/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/teaching/ml_18/</guid>
      <description>CS780 / CS880: Machine Learning Please see the main class website for detailed up to date information.
When and Where Mon &amp;amp; Wed, 11:10 am - 12:40 pm in Kingsbury N113
Class Content The goal of this class is to teach you how to use machine learning to understand data and make predictions in practice. The class will cover the fundamental concepts and algorithms in machine learning and data science as well as a wide variety of practical algorithms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/teaching/ml_19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/teaching/ml_19/</guid>
      <description>CS750 / CS850: Machine Learning Please see the main class website for detailed up-to-date information.
When and Where Mon &amp;amp; Wed, 11:10 am - 12:40 pm in Spaulding Life Sciences Hall G26 Fri: 11:00 am (recitation)
Class Content The goal of this class is to teach you how to use machine learning to understand data and make predictions in practice. The class will cover the fundamental concepts and algorithms in machine learning and data science as well as a wide variety of practical algorithms.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/teaching/opt_19/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/teaching/opt_19/</guid>
      <description>CS757/CS857: Mathematical Optimization for Applications Co-taught with Mark Lyon.
When and Where Mon &amp;amp; Wed, 9:40 am - 11:00 am Wed: Recitation
Class Content The goal of the class is to teach the foundations that underlie mathematical optimization techniques. The methods play an important role in machine learning, operations research, applied mathematics, industrial engineering.
 Unconstrained optimization methods   Gradient descent and line search Trust region methods Newton and Quasi-Newton methods (BFGS) Constrained optimization problems Lagrange multiplies and KKT conditions Linear and quadratic programming Convex analysis  Programming Language MATLAB, Python, R, or Julia</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/tutorials/risk/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorials/risk/</guid>
      <description>AAAI-2017: Tutorial on Risk-averse Decision Making and Control Presenters:
 Marek Petrik, University of New Hampshire Mohammad Ghavamzadeh, Adobe Research  Location: Continental 1-3, Ballroom Level
Schedule  9:00AM - 9:20AM: Introduction to risk-averse modeling 9:20AM - 9:40AM: Value at Risk and Conditional Value at Risk 9:40AM - 9:50AM: Break 9:50AM - 10:30AM: Coherent Measures of Risk: Properties and methods 10:30AM - 11:00AM: Coffee break 11:00AM - 12:00PM: Risk-averse reinforcement learning 12:00PM - 12:15PM: Break 12:15PM - 12:45PM: Time consistent measures of risk  Slides  Coherent Measures of Risk (Dynamic and Static) Risk-averse Reinforcement Learning  Detailed Description Traditional decision methods in artificial intelligence focus on maximizing the expected return (or minimizing the expected cost).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>/tutorials/robustrl/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/tutorials/robustrl/</guid>
      <description>Robust Reinforcement Learning This is a tutorial on robust reinforcement learning that was presented on 7/31/2019 as a part of the Deep Learning and Reinforcement Learning Summer School in Edmonton, Canada.
A slightly-edited version of the slides that were presented are here and an extended version is here.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
